10块钱的账单 我收到20块小费
I just got a $20 tip on a $10 check.
我可能是史上最棒女服务员
I may be the greatest waitress ever,
而奇怪的是 这事并没有让我想死
and strangely, that doesn't make me want to die.
干了好几年的活 你终于开窍了
You're finally getting the hang of a job you've had for years.
你的姓是奥巴马吗
Is your last name Obama?
又收到慷慨小费
Another big tip.
大概因为我的笑容吧
I think it's my smile.
的确是有东西在开口笑
Well, something's smiling.
上菜 吐司夹奶酪牛肉
Pickup. Patty melt.
改正 是屁股夹内裤
Correction: panty melt.
-卡洛琳 你... -干嘛 麦克斯
- Caroline, you have... - What, Max?
我为工作表现良好自豪吗
Pride in a job well done?
没错 我俩之中有人还能感到自豪
Yes, some of us can still feel pride.
是啊 但是十秒后就要破功了
Yeah, but only for about another ten seconds.
卡洛琳
Caroline.
要命啊
Oh, no.
这让我想起看到我妈侧乳时的情况
This reminds me of when I saw my mother's side boob.
麦克斯 你说说她啊
Max, you have to say something.
卡洛琳
Um, Caroline?
你看
Hey, look!
这男的给我10块钱小费
I just got a $10 tip from this guy,
可我把咖啡洒到他脸上了呢
and I spilled coffee on his face.
管它的
Screw it.
我也要靠着屁股发家致富
I'm taking the ass train to Money Town.
不行 没穿内裤
Oh, nope. Not wearing underwear.
我知道按理说有大单是好事
I know it's technically good to have a big order,
可是我再做五个小蛋糕
but I am five cupcakes away
就要患上医生称为恐龙手的病了
from what professional doctors call T.Rex arm.
像你平时教我的那样 用另一只手
Like you always tell me-- use your other hand.
会感觉像陌生人帮你"做"
It'll feel like a stranger.
快瞧咱们的店标贴纸
And how about our new business labels
以及我对任何事都能嗨的本事
and my ability to be excited about literally anything?
我用你存来买
I got them with the money you were saving
猪小弟大麻烟斗买的
for that Porky Pig bong.
抽到剩渣渣的时候
But when it's down to just resin,
可以看到"就这么多了"的字样
it says, "That's all, folks."
等我从订货人那里拿到钱就还
I'll pay you back as soon as we get the money
这笔大单是由"偶"订的吗
for this big order for...L?
麦克斯 有个叫"偶"的人订了这些小蛋糕吗
Max, someone named L ordered these cupcakes?
那不是"偶" 那是"我"
Oh, that's not an L; that's an I.
抱歉 我印刷体是从绑架信拼贴的字学的
Sorry, I learned printing mostly from ransom notes.
"我"
I?
什么样的人会取这种名字啊
I mean, what kind of person would just be named I?
我这样的人
This kind.
你们好 那是我下的单
Hello. That's my order.
好的 马上就好 这位先 生...
Yes, they're just about ready, mis...ter...
我还是省了你紧张跟困惑的功夫吧 亲
I'll spare you the stress and confusion, dear,
因为从你毛孔的粗细来看
because I can tell by the size of your pores,
你肯定很会冒汗
you're a sweater.
她的确是
She is.
她有时候看《全美超模大赛》会紧张冒汗到
Sometimes she gets so nervous watching "America's Next Top Model,"
让沙发像泡水过一样
our couch is slick for days.
剧透警告 节目里没有人会成为美国下一任超模
Spoiler alert: none of them are America's next top model.
我先说清楚 我不是他也不是她
To be clear, I am neither he nor she,
不是先生也不是小姐 不是男性也不是女性
Mr. nor Mrs., male nor female,
而我身上唯一会变化的
and the only part of me that's transitioning
只有我白天到晚上换着穿的高跟鞋
are my heels from day to evening.
我就是我 无法被贴标签的我
I am simply I, and I cannot be labeled.
我是流性人
I am gender fluid.
这挺酷啊
That's cool.
只要别"流"到我们身上就行
As long as none of it gets on us.
我的订单是好了呢 还是再忍着
Is my order ready, or do I have to wade through
看你们这对山寨版的艾米与蒂娜
more of this poor man's Amy and Tina?
我觉得我们更像是艾克与蒂娜
I like to think of us more as an Ike and Tina.
差不多快装盒完毕了
I'm just finishing boxing them up for you.
你的小蛋糕是可以放盒子[阴户]里的吧
It's okay for cupcakes to still be put in a box, right?
就不放进别人身体里而已
Just not people.
我要用你们的小蛋糕做些表演艺术
I'm using your cupcakes in some performance art.
"我"这个月是一名表演艺术家
See, I is a performance artist this month.
上个月"我"是在第八街的冰激凌点里工作
Last month, I was working at the Cold Stone Creamery on 8th Street.
我在那里面做过爱
Well, I've had sex there.
谁没在里面"做"过啊
Yes, well, who hasn't?
观众们会咬一口你们精致粉红
The audience will bite into one of your pretty, pink,
女性化的小蛋糕 咬完发现
femme-looking cupcakes, only to discover
我在里面塞了根"小香肠"
that I have inserted a cocktail weenie inside.
可谁会想被小香肠给惊到啊
But who wants to be surprised by a little weenie?
我不介意
I don't mind it.
这是个互动性实验
It's an interactive experiment
挑战我们直觉性互相贴标签的方法
that challenges how we instinctively label one another.
但我无需跟你们解释我的作品
But I don't have to explain my performance piece to you.
你们又不是我在新学院的老师
You're not my advisor at The New School.
原谅我
Forgive me.
我不是在批评你的东西
I wasn't criticizing your piece.
对啊 我们都不知道你有没有"那根东西"
Yeah, we're still not even sure if you have one.
能稍等一下吗
Can you excuse us for a minute?
对了 你的女衬衫上的紫红色
And by the way, the fuchsia in your blouse
把你的红胡子衬托得很美
really brings out the red in your beard.
大家以后看到我们可爱的标签
People are gonna see our adorable labels
会联想到我们的小蛋糕里面塞了小香肠
and think all our cupcakes are stuffed with wieners.
你的"小蛋糕"里塞了根
Would it kill you to have a wiener
"小香肠"是会死咩
stuffed in your cupcake?
付钱的大爷付了钱
Look, someone is paying for them,
想对小蛋糕干嘛就干嘛
and that someone can do whatever the hell they want with them.
我对买了我孩子的人也是这么说
I said the same thing to the people who bought my kids.
我们的小蛋糕不能被人丑化
We don't want someone to deface our cupcakes.
我们的小蛋糕是要给孩子
They're meant to be enjoyed by children
或浪漫喜剧情节跟自己故事太像的
or single women when a romantic comedy
单身女郎享用
hits too close to home.
钱就是钱 其他那些事无所谓
Money is money. It doesn't matter.
赶紧把小蛋糕装起来就是了
Just put the cupcakes in the bag.
我觉得这样不好
I don't feel good about this.
抱歉 我们不乐意卖小蛋糕给你
Sorry, but we're just not comfortable selling you our cupcakes.
他人都来了 快装 使劲咯[死基佬]
He is right here. Bag it!
你刚才叫我什么
What did you just call me?
-不是 -不是的
- Oh, no. - Oh, no.
不是不是不是
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
我没有说你以为我说的那个词
I did not say the thing you thought I said.
我连想都没想过
I didn't even think it.
其实 你说的屁话我有一半都没听进去
In fact, I wasn't listening to half that crap you said.
她说"使劲咯"[装袋] 是指像男人般
She said, "bag it," with a B, as in boy--
或不像男人般
or not a boy.
我懂你们是什么意思了
Oh, I see what this is.
这里又是一家恐同蛋糕店
This is just another homophobic bakery
不愿意对我们这种人提供服务
trying to deny service to people like me.
我不必站在这里
Well, I don't have to stand here
跟你们说我有多伤心
to tell you how upset I am.
我可以上点评网慢慢写
That's what Yelp is for.
惨了
Oh, no.
我觉得"凯西·贝兹"一定恨死我们了
I think Kathy Bates is really mad at us.
这下好了
Well, that sucks.
想到她就会让我想吃热狗
Now I want a hot dog.
客人们都上哪去了
Where are all the customers?
我上次见到这么少人 是在...
I haven't seen this few people since...
你用约炮软件的时候吗
You went on Tinder?
你的少女16岁生日派对吗
Your sweet 16 party?
卡洛琳 你也来一个
Caroline, throw one in there.
你上非诚勿扰的时候吗
Your season of "The Bachelor"?
我本来是要说
I was going to say
像小蛋糕窗口搞打折却没人来的时候
so few people since a sale at your cupcake window.
虐了你们一顿
Boom! I just schooled you.
哪有一顿 顶多一口
Well, preschooled us.
大家安安
Hey, everybody.
我的老天
Oh, my gosh.
我冲来这里的速度快到
You girls, I raced over here so fast,
我一半的头发还在市中心
I left half my hair in Midtown.
爱死你的女式头巾了 宝贝
Love the babushka, baby.
让我想起我的一位阿姨
Reminds me of my Aunt Schmirna.
奶子超赞 一边木瓜奶 一边荷包蛋
Great boobs: one big, one small.
各种口味的人都能满足
Something for everyone.
同志族群对你们超级火大啊
Yeah, the gays, they're real mad at you.
我的发型设计师卡尔跟我说在布鲁克林
Yeah, my stylist, Carl, told me about two girls
有俩小姑娘开小蛋糕店
with a cupcake shop in Brooklyn
拒绝服务"LGBTQ"族群的人
who didn't want to serve a member of the LGBTQ community.
LGBTQ吗
LGBTQ?
我上班就是坐这几号线的地铁来的
Those are the trains I take to get here.
天啊 麦克斯 这太糟糕了
Oh, my God. Max, this is terrible.
对啊
I know.
厄尔家离这里就一个街区
Earl only lives a block away.
他为什么要转五班地铁啊
Why is he taking five trains?
同志们气得冒烟了
The gays are steaming mad.
如果我是你们俩
You know, if I were you girls,
我就会远离同性恋大本营的那区
I would stay away from the Village,
东河 哈德逊河
the East River, the Hudson River,
住纽约的演员梅丽莎·里弗斯[河]
Melissa Rivers,
同志最爱的酸奶铺
Pinkberry,
同志最爱去的百老汇
Broadway.
你们这辈子也别想去给狗买衣服了
Yeah, and good luck shopping for dog clothes.
别这样 苏菲 哪有这么糟
Come on, Sophie. It's not that bad.
什么没那么糟
Not that bad?
如果没那么糟
If it wasn't that bad,
我头发弄完时会是这副德行吗
would I have left the salon looking like this?
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
他们这样就送客啦
They sent you out like that?
他们真是恨透我们了
They do hate us!
对啊 这还用说
I know. Tell me about it.
我看起来就像川普
I look like Donald Trump
还没把那像死猫一样的假发贴上脑袋前
before they Velcroed that dead cat to his head.
一个经典喜忧参半的消息
A classic good news/ bad news situation.
喜的是 我知道客人都上哪里去了
Good news: I figured out where all the customers are.
忧的是 他们都激动地在外面抗议小蛋糕店
Bad news: they're aggressively protesting your cupcake shop.
你去了廉价理发厅对吧
You went to Supercuts, didn't you?
希望你们现在高兴了
I hope you're happy, girls.
现在连阿憨都觉得自己比我强了
Now even Han thinks he's better than me.
蛋糕≠歧视
No cake equals hate.
好吧 情况不容乐观
Okay, this is bad.
我上次看见那么多愤怒的基佬
I haven't seen this many angry gay people
还是看NBC台的《彼得潘》时
since that NBC "Peter Pan."
主角来了
There they are.
就是那个人拒绝卖我小蛋糕
That's the one that refused to sell me cupcakes.
好啦 别这样
Hey, all right, come on now.
是香肠嘴的那个
The one with the bee-stung lips,
还是留着倒霉斜刘海的那个
or the one with the unfortunate side bang?
这只是个误会
This is just a misunderstanding.
麦克斯自制小蛋糕支持同性恋
Max's Homemade Cupcakes is pro-gay.
-我爱同性恋 -她的确是
- I love gay people. - She does.
她几乎只跟他们约会
She's pretty much dated them exclusively.
这个小门店是我们的梦想
This little business is our dream.
♪ 我仍怀抱昔日梦想 ♪
♪ I dreamed a dream ♪
♪ 纵使时光飞逝 ♪
♪ In time gone by ♪
♪ 当时希望闪耀 生活充满阳光 ♪
♪ When hope was high and life worth living ♪
♪ 我梦想爱永不凋零 ♪
♪ I dreamed that love would never die ♪
你做错梦了 金发妞
Wrong dream, blondie.
蛋糕≠歧视
No cake equals hate.
-蛋糕≠歧视 -我打给所有前任
- No cake equals hate. - I've called every one
让他们过来声援我
of my exes to come down and vouch for me,
而他们却冷落我
and they're freezing me out.
就像我是来求他们跟我做爱还是干嘛的
It's like I'm asking them for sex again or something.
我本来确信这事会有所好转
I was sure this would clear up on its own,
不过我总是这么想
but I always think that
因为我买不起青霉素[治性病]
because I can't afford penicillin.
餐厅还是没人来
The diner's still empty.
你们俩是祸害自己的生意没意思了
Did you two get bored killing your own business
于是决定来祸害我的吗
and decide to go after mine?
我敢代表所有的女人说一句
I can say, on behalf of all women,
我们对你的"小生意"没兴趣
none of us are ever going after your business.
显然你没见过玛莎
Apparently you've never met Martha,
我小区药店的一个饥渴肥婆收银员
the portly cashier at my neighborhood Rite Aid.
我要去跟他们说说 捋直他们的想法
I'm gonna go talk to them, set them straight.
鉴于他们都是弯的 我只能尽力而为
Well, as much as I can, given the circumstances.
我们被困在这里两天了
We have been trapped in here for two days.
就像是被关在基达那摩湾[监狱]
It's like we're in Gaytanamo Bay.
我要打开这扇窗 叫他们滚蛋
I'm gonna open this window and tell them to screw off.
言论自由
Free speech.
你的幼小心灵受伤了
Your feelings got hurt.
真遗憾 太惨了
Too bad, so sad.
老天
Oh...my God.
你应该把该死的小蛋糕卖给他
You should have sold him the damn cupcakes.
我是雪儿 蛋糕婊
I'm Cher, bitch.
发生什么事了
What happened?
雪儿也恨咱们了
Cher hates us too.
我们一定是做错了
We must be wrong.
那不是雪儿 麦克斯
That's not the Cher, Max.
那是雪儿模仿者
It's a Cher impersonator.
那我为什么会起鸡皮
Then why do I have chills?
我爱雪儿
I love Cher.
我以前常幻想她才是我的亲妈
I used to imagine she was my real mom
总有一天会来接我
and that one day she'd pick me up
把我接回她的身边
and take me away with her,
然后我们一起穿配套的透明情趣连身袜
and then we'd get matching see-through body stockings
就像普通的母女那样
like normal mothers and daughters.
那画面真恶心
Aw, that's so disturbing.
麦克斯 我们没有错
Max, we did nothing wrong.
你不能因为某个
You can't just back down
模仿女性的人而打退堂鼓
because of some female impersonator.
你变金发了
Now you're blonde.
听着 雪儿 我们没有错
Look, Cher, we did nothing wrong.
听着 我要一个小蛋糕
Hey, look. I want a cupcake,
而且没人 我是指没有任何人
and nobody-- and I mean nobody--
能扫爷的兴
is gonna rain on my parade.
各位注意
Attention, everyone.
各位注意了
这是隔壁餐厅的老板
This is the owner of the diner next door,
他有话要说
and he has something to say,
所以大家先听这位"同志"说几句
so let's listen to our gay comrade.
我不是弯的同志
Oh, I'm not gay.
怪不得穿这么没品味的毛衣背心
Well, that explains the sweater vest.
对 我是直的 喜欢女人
Yep, I'm straight. Love the ladies.
我可是吸妞石哦
I'm a bit of a chick magnet.
你都没有冰箱吸铁石那么大
You're barely the size of a refrigerator magnet.
听
There.
又一句不友善的话
Another insensitive remark,
这次是攻击侏儒族群的人
this time about the little people community,
就像我身旁这位"小"朋友
just like my friend here.
我才不是小人国的好吗
Oh, I'm not a little person.
麦克斯 千万别说话
Max, do not say anything.
好吧
Fine.
但这里曾经是美国
But this used to be America,
自由之乡 羞辱之地
home of the free and land of the insult.
各位 或许我能为大家澄清一下
Everyone, maybe I can clear this up.
那个女人不讨厌同性恋人群
That woman over there doesn't hate gay people.
-她讨厌所有人群 -没错
- She hates all people. - Yeah.
蛋糕≠歧视
No cake equals hate.
苏菲 你在干什么啊
Sophie, what are you doing?
抱歉 姑娘们
Oh, hi. Sorry, girls.
蛋糕≠歧视
No cake equals hate.
拜托公平公正 复原我的秀发
Hey, be fair and fix my hair.
抱歉 打扰了
Hi. Excuse me.
不是吧 我们还说了
Oh, no, did we also say something
冒犯户外运动品牌的话吗
to offend the L.L.Bean community?
麦克斯 现在连直男都不爽我们了
Max, now straight people are mad at us too.
餐厅的收银员说
The cashier in the diner said
最好从这个门进来找你们
this was the best way to get to you.
他还说他的CD只卖5.99块 实在很划算
He also told me his CD was a bargain at $5.99.
真不敢相信那群抗议者能让你过来
I can't believe you got past the protestors.
我还以为那些男孩
I would have thought those boys
会把"后门"守得紧紧的
would have the back door covered.
天啊 外面那些人真的很疯狂
Man, it's crazy out there, right?
我是说 别人怎么做生意
I mean, however people run their business
是别人的事
should be their own business.
以前为贩毒集团工作时
That was always the company line
我们的口号就是这样
when I worked for that cartel.
我在网上得知你们俩的处境
I read about your situation on the internet,
我想订购500个小蛋糕
and I want to order 500 cupcakes.
请问你有老婆吗
Is there a Mrs. L.L.Bean?
有 婚姻幸福美满15年
There is. Happily married 15 years.
我是特里·威廉姆斯
Terry Williams.
"家为本 家至上 家第一"
"Family Foremost Foundation"?
对 家家家
Yep, the FFF.
哇 三个家
Wow, three of them.
你们有好多家需要好好"搞"啊
You people really like a good F.
我们是一群个体户 就像你们
Well, we're a group of independent business owners like you.
周日会到这里开个大会
We're in town for a convention on Sunday.
信息都在卡片上了
Information is on the card.
我们一定会带着500个小蛋糕去
We'll bet there with 500 cupcakes.
特里 你们要什么样的小蛋糕
Oh, Terry, what kind of cupcakes?
你们的生意 你们说了算
It's your business. You decide.
-麦克斯 这下怎么样 -我知道
- Max, how about that? - I know.
这位像某厨房纸代言人的哥们拯救了我们
The Brawny paper towel guy just saved our asses.
下午好 家人们
Good afternoon, family.
下午好 特里
Good afternoon, Terry.
听到"家"这个字后面不是接"庭法院"
It's so weird for me to hear the word "Family"
我感觉好奇怪啊
not followed by the word "Court."
希望大家还有精力
I hope you have some energy left
欢迎我们家庭的领袖
for the leader of our family,
他总是把家放在第一位
the man who always puts family foremost,
大丹兄
Brother Dan.
下午好 家人们
Good afternoon, family.
下午好 大丹兄
Good afternoon, Brother Dan.
谢谢你 特里兄
And thank you, Brother Terry,
这么热情地介绍我
for that warm introduction.
他们是黏住了吗
Are they stuck?
我们大丹兄的计划里
Um, I think there might be one more F
还要搞一家
in Brother Dan's plan.
今天我们来到这里 庆祝最完美的联盟
Today, we are here to celebrate that most perfect union:
家
the family.
我们在家里感到欢乐
We rejoice in the family.
我们为家而活而爱
We live, we love,
为家饥渴
we lust...
当然是健康的那种
wholesomely, of course, for the family.
今天我们的大家庭多了两位新女儿
And today, our family has found two new daughters.
姑娘们 你们何不上台露个脸
Girls, why don't you come up on stage?
你不会想让她上台的
Oh, you don't want her to get on stage.
老实说 你何不在她又开口唱歌之前
In fact, why don't you get that spotlight off us
把打在我俩身上的聚光灯挪走
before she starts to sing again?
别害羞嘛 你们俩姑娘敢于挑战
Don't be shy. You two girls went up
当代强迫政治立场正确的黑手党
against today's politically correct mafia.
你们抵制家的破坏者
You stood up to the family destroyers,
抵制他们黝黑的皮肤 裸露的上身
with their tan, shirtless torsos
抵制他们免费的在线黄片
and their free online pornography.
快上来抱抱
Come on up for a hug.
上来吧
Come on.
就从楼梯旁边走过 然后直接走掉
Just walk past the stairs and keep going.
多少钱都不值得跟这群人摊上关系
No money is worth being part of whatever this is.
趁人不注意就赶紧溜
Let's make a break for it.
我们准备了大惊喜哦
And we have a big surprise.
这有一张支票是给麦克斯自制小蛋糕的
Here's a check made out to Max's Homemade Cupcakes
面值一万美元
for $10,000!
我们拿了支票再溜吧
Let's make a break for it after we get the check.
这周的每一个夜晚 我都在我挚爱的妻子
Every night this week, I have wept in the arms
佩吉的怀里失声痛哭
of my loving wife, Peggy.
我为这两位姑娘的困境而哭
I have wept about the plight of these two girls,
我非常感激我们可以齐心协力
and I am very thankful that we could all pull together
来减轻她们的痛苦
to ease their pain.
麦克斯 卡洛琳
Max, Caroline,
靠近我
come closer to me.
靠近
Closer?
他知道我们没有小鸡鸡吗
Does he know we don't have penises?
来近点 我好给你们
Come close so I can present you
这张大支票
your giant check.
真希望我把我的大钱包带来了
I just wish I'd brought my giant wallet.
没人需要知道我们拿了他们的钱
No one has to know we're getting money from them.
此时此刻 几百万的人们在看着这幕
Right now, millions of people are watching
因为我们在网上全球同步现场直播
as we stream live around the world.
现在是现场直播吗
Oh, this is streaming right now?
麦克斯 这在现场直播啊
Max, this is streaming.
我也激动得在现场漏了点尿
I'm streaming a little in my pants about this check.
此时此刻 世界各地
Right now, all around the world,
人们看见了什么是道德
people are seeing what morals look like.
这两位姑娘敢于对抗
These are the girls who are standing up
那些离经叛道者 离婚者
against the deviants, the divorces,
科学家 嘻哈爱好者
the scientists, the hip-hop lovers,
以及...
and...
大麻吸食者
the doobie smokers.
我虽然也不喜欢人和科学
I don't like people or science, either,
但正当的大麻有什么错
but ain't nothing wrong with a righteous doob.
我们要告诉世界我们再也不会容忍
We need to show the world that we will not tolerate
那些离经叛道者和堕落的人
these deviants and these degenerates any longer!
我不想跟这些人扯上半毛钱关系
I don't want to be associated with these people.
同性恋们会永远恨我们 我以后有房子的话
The gays will hate us forever, and when I get an interior,
我还指望找同性恋设计师装修呢
I want it decorated.
全世界的人们都在看
People watching everywhere,
这就是我们家庭的两位新面孔
meet the two new faces of family.
你知道我们该怎么做 对吧
You know what we have to do, right?
数到三
On the count of three.
一 二
One, two...
别看 佩吉
Look away, Peggy!
抱我 特里
Hold me, Terry.
我相信这是你的
I believe this is yours.
饮品都供应不过来了
I can't keep up with all these drinks.
小伞快用光了
I'm running out of tiny umbrellas.
那下雨你怎么回家呀
How will you get home if it rains?
没错 是我
Yes, it's I.
在网上看见你俩的吻照了
Saw your kiss on Instagram,
我想为整个闹剧道歉
and I wanted to apologize for the whole mix-up.
我的确是有点过于敏感
I can be a little overly sensitive.
不信可以问问兰蔻的柜姐
Just ask anyone that works at Lancome.
她们都认识我
Oh, they know me at Lancome.
她们称我为蹭试用品狂魔
They call me No More Free Samples.
听着 我明白
Listen, I get it.
没有人希望被贬低至某些标签
Nobody wants to be reduced to some label.
讨厌人是需要其他原因的
You should hate people for other reasons:
可以是因为他们恶心或毒舌
because they're gross or mean
或是你欠他们钱
or you owe them money.
到头来
At the end of the day,
我们只是想凑合过日[得到双性恋]
we are all just trying to get by.
"双"性恋 我可不信任那些人
Bi? Now, those people I don't trust.
抱歉我来晚了 姑娘们
Hi, sorry I'm late for the party, girls,
但我刚在外面跟我的新朋友聊天
but I was just outside talking to my new friends,
鸡冠头丽莎和芽龈研
Lisa Newcar and Ginger Vitis.
我们的鞋码都一样哦
We all wear the same shoe size!
姑娘们 姑娘们
Ah, ladies, ladies.
我很想留下来庆祝
I would love to stay and celebrate,
但我有约了
but I've got a hot date
跟四号桌的年轻小妞
with that fine young thing at table four.
不错嘛 厄尔
Good for you, Earl.
但我不知道那到底是不是女人
But I don't know if that's exactly a woman.
姑娘们 我都快80岁了
Ladies, I'm almost 80.
我不知道男女这件事还是不是问题
I don't know that that's exactly a problem.
我和几个姑娘筹了点款
A few of the girls and I took up a collection
作为前两天让你们停业的补偿
for shutting your business down the last couple days,
给
so here.
雪儿 你居然送我礼物
Cher, you got me a present?
我等这一刻等了一辈子啊
I've waited for this my whole life.
你知道我其实叫查德 对吧
You know my name is Chad, right?
要振作起来
So snap out of it!